Maddy Lok // Full-Stack Engineer

Driven full-stack engineer with experience in several languages including Python, Javascript, SQL, React, and C++. As a result of my history as a pre-medical student with varied healthcare work experience, I excel under pressure in stressful environments while remaining efficient and communicative.

maddy.lok04@gmail.com Los Angeles, CA

Work Experience

Brown Bear Apothecary / Web Developer

January 2023 - March 2023, Remote

- Coding a fully functioning e-commerce website utilizing HTML, Javascript, Ruby on Rails, and CSS.
- In charge of designing the user interface and experience.

ScribeAmericaLLC / Medical Scribe

November 2021 - August 2022, Los Alamitos, CA

- Accompanied physicians throughout fast-paced, high-stress environments.
- Utilized Cerner electronic medical records system.
- Documented information about examinations, treatment plans, lab results, etc. directly into patient charts.
- Reviewed records, paperwork, and orders for errors and resolved issues with minimal direction.
- Stayed on top of large patient loads to facilitate efficient and organized workflow.
- Used strong communication skills with providers, nurses, and other ER staff to ensure no information was missing from patient records.

University of California, Irvine Medical Center / Medical Research Intern June 2019 - February 2020, Irvine, CA

- Authored an abstract for "Predictors of Risk Factors for Discharge to Skilled Nursing Facilities in Adult Trauma Patients".
- Compiled data from hospital records, utilized SQL and Microsoft Excel to input and organize data, and produced timely reports.
- Gathered, arranged, and ensured correct data to create representative graphs and charts highlighting results for presentations.
- Worked alongside the chief of trauma surgery and surgical residents.
- Presented abstract at a surgical conference in Orlando, Florida in Feb 2020.

Education

NYU Tandon School of Engineering / Computer Science/Engineering Certification

January 2022 - June 2022

Relevant coursework: C++.

Loyola University Chicago / B.S. Biochemistry

August 2017 - May 2021, Chicago, IL

Cum laude, Minor in photography, Interdisciplinary Honors Program, Dean's List 6 Terms, Kappa Kappa Gamma member and Council member, Captain of Women's club basketball.

Projects

Pokemon Zero-Sum Game

Github:

https://github.com/maddylok/rockpaperscissors

A digital implementation of a zero-sum game themed under Pokemon.

 Developed with HTML, CSS, and Javascript.

Calculator

Github:

https://github.com/maddylok/calculator

Functional scientific calculator

Song Review App (In progress)

Utilizing Python and Heroku to build an app for reviewing and sharing songs with friends.

Certifications

Data Scientist with Python

DataCamp

Skills

Javascript

DataGrips

Heroku

Python

React

HTML

CSS

C++ SQL

Figma

.g...a

Ruby on Rails

Microsoft Office Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop